<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Wizard City</title>
    <link href="https://wizard.city/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://wizard.city" />
    <updated>2024-08-11T02:35:01+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>NinjaDuckie</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://wizard.city</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Discworld MUD</title>
        <author>
            <name>NinjaDuckie</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://wizard.city/discworld-mud/"/>
        <id>https://wizard.city/discworld-mud/</id>
        <media:content url="https://wizard.city/media/posts/6/Ankh-Morpork.png" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-08-11T02:35:01+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://wizard.city/media/posts/6/Ankh-Morpork.png" alt="Kefka&#x27;s map of the city of Ankh-Morpork." />
                    This free-to-play text-based adventure game set in the mostly-flat, circular world-supported-by-elephants-on-a-space-turtle conceived by the late Sir Terry Pratchett has been running since 1992. I had the privilege of becoming a member of the development team in 2023 and learned some aging C# systems for creating&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://wizard.city/media/posts/6/Ankh-Morpork.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="Kefka&#x27;s map of the city of Ankh-Morpork." /></p>
                <p>This <a href="https://discworld.starturtle.net/lpc/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">free-to-play text-based adventure game</a> set in the mostly-flat, circular world-supported-by-elephants-on-a-space-turtle conceived by the late Sir Terry Pratchett has been running since 1992. I had the privilege of becoming a member of the development team in 2023 and learned some aging C# systems for creating content therein.</p>
<p>The development team is incredibly encouraging and welcoming to new developers, and the community still thrives after 30 years, with things like <a href="https://dw.daftjunk.com/index.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Kefka's map &amp; item database</a> (left, the map of Ankh-Morpork) or Quow's <a href="https://quow.co.uk/mushclient.php" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">dedicated MUSHclient package</a> replete with various plugins that allow the playerbase to engage with a number of QoL improvements.</p>
<p><code>GNU Terry Pratchett.</code></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Opus 2</title>
        <author>
            <name>NinjaDuckie</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://wizard.city/opus-2/"/>
        <id>https://wizard.city/opus-2/</id>
        <media:content url="https://wizard.city/media/posts/5/idrc.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-05-30T02:35:11+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://wizard.city/media/posts/5/idrc.jpg" alt="" />
                    I started at Opus 2 in 2012 as a temp. Within half a year I was in their technical team, delivering hardware solutions for court and arbitration transcriptions, and helping pioneer the prototype of their flagship product, Magnum, a unified legal proceedings platform for evidence,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://wizard.city/media/posts/5/idrc.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>I started at <a href="https://www.opus2.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Opus 2</a> in 2012 as a temp. Within half a year I was in their technical team, delivering hardware solutions for court and arbitration transcriptions, and helping pioneer the prototype of their flagship product, Magnum, a unified legal proceedings platform for evidence, arguments, transcripts, comms, etc.</p>
<p>In the five years that followed, I prepared the Singapore office and trained staff in the Singapore supreme court, and provided on-site assistance at private arbitration sites including Osaka, Miami, Geneva, the Hague, and even St. Vincent &amp; the Grenadines.</p>
<p>When I was not globetrotting or working in the courts, I provided internal IT support, assisted with production and delivery of printed and digital transcripts, produced 3D marketing videos to demonstrate new product solutions, and kept morale up running after-hours tabletop games nights midweek.</p>
<p>I departed Opus 2 in 2017 when I was headhunted by <a href="https://wizard.city/harneys/" rel="nofollow">a different firm</a>.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Harneys</title>
        <author>
            <name>NinjaDuckie</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://wizard.city/harneys/"/>
        <id>https://wizard.city/harneys/</id>
        <media:content url="https://wizard.city/media/posts/4/harneys.png" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-05-30T02:54:20+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://wizard.city/media/posts/4/harneys.png" alt="" />
                    I joined Harney Westwood &amp; Riegels LLP as a Contract Express specialist, converting complex legal &amp; government forms into human-readable documents. After six months, I transitioned into IT, becoming lead Operations Engineer for the London, Luxembourg and Cyprus offices, and providing support for the Hong&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://wizard.city/media/posts/4/harneys.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>I joined <a href="https://www.harneys.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Harney Westwood &amp; Riegels LLP</a> as a <a href="https://www.thomsonreuters.in/en/products-services/legal/contract-express.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contract Express</a> specialist, converting complex legal &amp; government forms into human-readable documents. After six months, I transitioned into IT, becoming lead Operations Engineer for the London, Luxembourg and Cyprus offices, and providing support for the Hong Kong, British Virgin Islands &amp; Cayman Islands offices.</p>
<p>I served as a fixture of the IT department and assisted staff in all twelve of our office sites through the ticketing system and on the phone. I led deployment of multiple IT systems, and wrote various papers on how to improve processes.</p>
<p>In this role I took ownership of Airwatch and on-site biometric security. During the COVID-19 pandemic, I supported Horizon virtual desktop infrastructure, distributed home office hardware, and was first point of contact for new user inductions across the three European offices.</p>
<p>I left Harneys in August 2022 to briefly join <a href="https://wizard.city/the-game-band/" rel="nofollow">The Game Band</a>, returning in 2024.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Game Band</title>
        <author>
            <name>NinjaDuckie</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://wizard.city/the-game-band/"/>
        <id>https://wizard.city/the-game-band/</id>
        <media:content url="https://wizard.city/media/posts/3/The-Game-Band-Website-Photo_2.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-05-29T13:35:32+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://wizard.city/media/posts/3/The-Game-Band-Website-Photo_2.jpg" alt="" />
                    I had been doing volunteer work with Blaseball from September of 2020; in August of 2022, I quit my existing job, and by December I was working for TGB on contract. Together with the six other paid members of the community team, and 21 volunteers,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://wizard.city/media/posts/3/The-Game-Band-Website-Photo_2.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>I had been doing volunteer work with Blaseball from September of 2020; in August of 2022, I quit my <a href="https://wizard.city/harneys/" rel="nofollow">existing job</a>, and by December I was working for TGB on contract.</p>
<p>Together with the six other paid members of the community team, and 21 volunteers, we successfully wrangled the whims of 30,000+ people in a Discord server, fostering communication skills and a caring attitude in the community as a whole while still maintaining an individual competitive spirit for each of the 24 teams.</p>
<p>While in this role I worked with a Discord bot called <a href="https://docs.carl.gg/#/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Carl</a>, personally setting up over 120 unique Tagscript snippets enabling members to interact with the bot and each other. I also supplemented existing graphics by <a href="https://imgur.com/a/blaseball-community-work-PXaOyx7" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">producing Discord "banners"</a> in Photoshop, highlighting recent important events in the game or community.</p>
<p>Blaseball was cancelled on June 2nd, 2023, and I moved back to IT work.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>WIZARD CITY?</title>
        <author>
            <name>NinjaDuckie</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://wizard.city/why-wizard-city/"/>
        <id>https://wizard.city/why-wizard-city/</id>
        <media:content url="https://wizard.city/media/posts/2/wizard-2021410_1280.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-05-29T13:19:12+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://wizard.city/media/posts/2/wizard-2021410_1280.jpg" alt="Photograph of Lego Gandalf minifig walking in the moss by Aitoff from Pixabay." />
                    wizard noun ˈwi-zərd ˈsi-tē &lt; BACK
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://wizard.city/media/posts/2/wizard-2021410_1280.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="Photograph of Lego Gandalf minifig walking in the moss by Aitoff from Pixabay." /></p>
                <h2>wizard    <em>noun</em></h2>
<p><em>ˈwi-zərd</em></p>
<ol>
<li>wielder of magic</li>
<li><strong>a very skillful person</strong></li>
</ol>
<h2>city    <em>noun</em></h2>
<p><em>ˈsi-tē</em></p>
<ol>
<li>an inhabited place of greater size, population, or importance than a town or village</li>
<li><strong>a fun and easy to remember top-level domain</strong></li>
</ol>
<p><a href="https://wizard.city" rel="nofollow">&lt; BACK</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
